
const SOUTHAMERICA = [{
    id: 1,
    question: 'Argentina',
    answer: 'Beunos Aires',
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: 'Bolivia',
    answer: 'Sucre',
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: 'Brazil',
    answer: 'Brasilia',
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: 'Chile',
    answer: 'Santiago',
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: 'Colombia',
    answer: 'Bogotá',
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: 'Ecuador',
    answer: 'Quito',
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: 'Guyana',
    answer: 'Georgetown',
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: 'Paraguay',
    answer: 'Asunción',
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: 'Peru',
    answer: 'Lima',
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: 'Suriname',
    answer: "Paramaribo",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: 'Uruguay',
    answer: 'Montevideo',
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: 'Venezuela',
    answer: 'Caracas',
  }
  ]

  export default SOUTHAMERICA;